Free shipping on over $99

* Outdoor
* Industrial
* Commercial
* Specialty
* Indoor

Need help?

Call us 770-299-4979

Follow Us

Back

* Area
* Street
* Wall Pack
* Landscape

Back

* High Bay
* Canopy

Back

* Tubes
* Panel / Troffer

Back

Back

* Strip Light
* Corn
* Bulbs
* Downlight
* Flush Mounts

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

 Clear

All categories All categoriesCabinet LightingCeiling LightChandelierLED BulbLED CanopyLED Cooler LightsLED Corn BulbLED Flood LightsLED Grow LightLED High BaysLED PanelLED Power SupplyLED Street LampLED Street LightsLED Strip LightLED TrofferLED Tube LightLED Wall PackLight BulbsModern LightPendant LightSocketSolar LED LightsWall Mount

Close

Login / Signup

[0

Cart](https://greenlightdepot.com/cart)

Spend $ 99.00 more and get free shipping!

Your cart is empty

Privacy Policy
==============

GreenLightDepot.com is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect your personal information.

### GreenLightDepot.com's Commitment to Security

GreenLightDepot.com encrypts billing information wherever requested online. Personal information is accessible only by staff designated to handle complaints or requests. All GreenLightDepot.com agents and contractors with access to personal information are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with GreenLightDepot.com

### Personal Information that GREENLIGHTDEPOT.COM May Collect

GreenLightDepot.com collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint and inquiry information.

GreenLightDepot.com may also collect business information from sole proprietorships some of which might constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity.

GreenLightDepot.com does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

### How GREENLIGHTDEPOT.COM May Use Personal Information

When you register for an account or subscribe to a newsletter, you will be asked to provide certain Personal Information, which we will use to fulfill your request.

Unless you consent, GreenLightDepot.com will use your personal information for the purpose for which it was submitted such as to reply to inquiries, handle your complaints and process billing and business requests, and we will use such information to provide operational notices, and in program record keeping and to conduct research on industry marketplace practices. Our research will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us.

Surveys: We may ask you to complete surveys or opinion polls from time to time. We only use the information that we collect from surveys in an aggregate manner, not in individually identifiable form.

### GREENLIGHTDEPOT.COM never sells or rents personal information.

We will also release personal information under the following circumstances:

* Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by an agency for governmental investigative purposes or governmental proceedings
* Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of
* To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

### Computer Tracking and Cookies

Our web site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by its visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

GreenLightDepot.com uses cookies, web beacons and similar technology to help you navigate the Services, to allow us to learn how you use the Services, and to improve the Services. Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not reveal any Personal Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Site. However, once you choose to provide Personal Information to the Services, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. If you decide not to permit cookies on your computer, this may affect your ability to use the Services.

### Problems

We are committed to adhering to our privacy policy and applicable laws and to making your online experience secure and valuable. If you have a question, request, complaint, dispute or concern related to this privacy policy, please contact us by emailing support@greenlightdepot.com.

Newsletter
----------

Subscribe to our newsletter and be the first to know about our latest products, special offers, and expert tips.

 Your email

Subscribe

1000 Laval Blvd,  
Lawrenceville, GA 30043  
support@greenlightdepot.com770.299.4979  
Monday - Friday 9am - 6pm EST

Overview

Company Policies

Resources

Dealer Account

 Email

 Password

Login

© 2024 Green Light Depot  

Follow Us

We Accept

American Express Apple Pay Diners Club Discover Google Pay Mastercard PayPal Shop Pay Visa

© 2024 Green Light Depot  

* Opens in a new window.
